Shatterproof.
The temperature drops in the empty room
A digital pulse in the silent gloom
I am watching the screen for a sign of life
Cutting the wire with a sterile knife
Shatterproof Behind a glass I'm watching you
move Shatterproof Nothing to break, nothing to
prove Cold to the touch And perfectly smooth
Shatterproof
The surface is clean and the edges are tight
I am locking the doors for the rest of the night
No static, no signal, no interference Just the
absolute zero of my appearance Shatterproof
Behind the glass I'm watching you move
Shatterproof Nothing to break, nothing to
prove Cold to the touch And perfectly smooth
Shatterproof
The pressure's rising But the structure will
hold The circuitry freezing
Out in the cold
Shatterproof
Behind the glass I'm watching you move
Nothing to prove Cold to the touch Unperfectly
smooth Shadowproof
Perfectly smooth
Shadowproof